The idea is that when you have a very
volatile move in Bitcoin,
whether it's to the upside or the
downside, once this metric starts to
reach pretty high activity levels,
it is oftentimes, again, not a guarantee
and markets can change.
The past is not necessarily a predictor
of the future, but you would expect this
metric to spike. And it's clearly not
spiking right now, right? Like there's
just simply not a lot of whale activity
as it stands right now. But that could
certainly change in a few months. We
also, of course, have the exchange
inflow composition and and whale holder
positioning. Now, what's interesting is
if you if you scroll down and look at
some of the charts, you have This is the
showing you whale transaction count for
100K plus, a million plus, and 10
million plus. You can see what I'm
talking about. Like if you're just
looking at transactions with 100,000
plus in in volume,
there's just not a lot going on right
now, right?